A Guide to the David Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1010 FA453
Rockefeller Archive Center
- David Rockefeller family photographs, 1932-1994; 1010
  - Prints, Approximately 2,165 prints
    - DR - Philanthropies - National Academy of Design, 1986; 1 prints (Box P 179, Folder 234)
    - DR - Philanthropies - National Urban League - Knoedler Gallery, 1959; 8 prints (Box P 179, Folder 235)
    - DR - Philanthropies - New York Botanical Garden - Peggy Rockefeller Rose Garden, 1988; 1 print (Box P 179, Folder 236)
    - DR - Philanthropies - New York Zoological Society, 1 print (Box P 179, Folder 237)
    - DR - Philanthropies - ORBIS, 1 print (Box P 179, Folder 238)
    - DR - Philanthropies - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Magsaysay Awardees Assembly - Bangkok, 1987; 1 print (Box P 179, Folder 239)
    - DR - Philanthropies - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - National Executive Service Corps. - Anniversary Luncheon, 1987 (Box P 179, Folder 240)
    - DR - Philanthropies - Rockefeller University, 1985; 1 print (Box P 179, Folder 241)
    - DR - Philanthropies - Rockefeller University - Duke of Westminster, 1986; 3 prints (Box P 179, Folder 242)
    - DR - Philanthropies - Rockefeller University - Founders Ball, 1985; 3 prints (Box P 179, Folder 243)
    - DR - Philanthropies - Rockefeller University - Founders Ball, 1987; 1 print (Box P 179, Folder 244)
    - DR - Philanthropies - Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research - Model, 1954; 14 prints (Box P 179, Folder 245)
    - DR - Philanthropies - Save the Children, 1981; 13 prints (Box P 179, Folder 246)
    - DR - Philanthropies - Summer Jobs 86, 1986 (Box P 179, Folder 247)
    - DR - Philanthropies - Summer Jobs 87, 1987; 2 prints (Box P 179, Folder 248)
    - DR - Philanthropies - United Nations - Dinner Party, 1986; 11 prints (Box P 179, Folder 249)
    - DR - Philanthropies - United Nations - Mikail Gorbachev Reception, 1986; 1 print (Box P 179, Folder 250)
    - DR - Philanthropies - United Negro College Fund, 1977; 1 print (Box P 179, Folder 251)
    - DR - Philanthropies - YWCA - Betty Lord, 1988; 5 prints (Box P 179, Folder 252)
    - DR - Portraits, 1 print (Box P 179, Folder 253)
    - DR - Portraits, 4 prints (Box P 179, Folder 254)
    - DR - Portraits, 1947; 4 prints (Box P 179, Folder 255)
    - DR - Portraits, 1949; 38 prints (Box P 179, Folder 256)
    - DR - Portraits, 1960; 11 prints (Box P 179, Folder 257)
    - DR - Portraits, 1964; 16 prints (Box P 179, Folder 258)
    - DR - Portraits, 1975; 1 print (Box P 179, Folder 259)
    - DR - Portraits, 1977; 1 print (Box P 179, Folder 260)
    - DR - Portraits, 1978; 2 prints (Box P 179, Folder 261)
    - DR - Portraits - Fabian Bachrach, 1947; 22 prints (Box P 180, Folder 262)
    - DR - Portraits - Chase Manhattan Bank - President of, 9 prints (Box P 180, Folder 263)
    - DR - Portraits - Chase Manhattan Bank - Vice President of, 13 prints (Box P 180, Folder 264)
    - DR - Portraits - Cover of "Institutional Investor", 1981; 3 prints (Box P 180, Folder 265)
    - DR - Portraits - Karsh, 3 prints (Box P 180, Folder 266)
    - DR - Portraits - Koshiba, 7 prints (Box P 180, Folder 267)
    - DR - Portraits - Lincoln School, 1932; 1 print (Box P 180, Folder 268)
    - DR - Portraits - New York Public Library, 1986; 1 print (Box P 180, Folder 269)
    - DR - Portraits - Paris, 5 prints (Box P 180, Folder 270)
    - DR - Portraits - Uniform, 2 prints (Box P 180, Folder 271)
    - DR - Travel - Egypt, 1980; 1 print (Box P 180, Folder 272)
    - DR - Travel - Philippines - Album, 1966; 16 prints (Box P 180, Folder 273)
    - DR - Travel - Russia - Leningrad, 1971; 34 prints (Box P 180, Folder 274)
    - Margaret McGrath (Peggy) Rockefeller, 1 print (Box P 180, Folder 275)
    - Margaret McGrath (Peggy) Rockefeller, 9 prints (Box P 180, Folder 276)
    - Margaret McGrath (Peggy) Rockefeller, 1973; 2 prints (Box P 180, Folder 277)
    - Margaret McGrath (Peggy) Rockefeller - Wedding, 1940; 14 prints (Box P 180, Folder 278)
    - Eileen McGrath Rockefeller - Wedding to Paul Growald, 1981; 14 prints (Box P 180, Folder 279)
    - Neva Rockefeller, 4 prints (Box P 180, Folder 280)
    - Neva Rockefeller, 1964; 15 prints and 1 contact sheet (Box P 180, Folder 281)
    - Group Portraits - Children, 3 prints (Box P 180, Folder 282)
    - Group Portraits - Family - DR and Peggy, 2 prints (Box P 180, Folder 283)
    - Group Portraits - Family - DR and Peggy - London, 1973; 1 print (Box P 180, Folder 284)
    - Group Portraits - Family, 8 prints (Box P 180, Folder 285)
    - Group Portraits - Family - DR - Steven Rockefeller, Jr., 1986; 1 print (Box P 180, Folder 286)
    - Group Portraits - Family, 1967; 1 print (Box P 180, Folder 287)
    - Group Portraits - Family, 1979; 3 prints (Box P 180, Folder 288)
    - Group Portraits - Family and Friends, 1 print (Box P 180, Folder 289)
    - Group Portraits - Family and Friends, 1 print (Box P 180, Folder 290)
    - Group Portraits - Family and Friends, 11 prints (Box P 180, Folder 291)
    - Group Portraits - Family and Friends - St. Barts, 1979; 1 print (Box P 180, Folder 292)
    - Group Portraits - Family and Friends - St. Barts, 1981 March; 1 print (Box P 180, Folder 293)
    - Group Portraits - Friends, 13 prints (Box P 180, Folder 294)
    - Group Portraits - Friends, 1 print (Box P 180, Folder 295)
    - Group Portraits - Friends - Beatty, 1984; 5 prints (Box P 180, Folder 296)
    - Group Portraits - Friends - Malcolm Forbes - Henry Kissinger - Rupert Murdoch, 1987; 2 prints (Box P 180, Folder 297)
    - Group Portraits - Friends - William Hewitt, 1988; 9 prints (Box P 180, Folder 298)
    - Group Portraits - Friends - B. Johnson - Brooke Astor - Donald Sraw, 1974; 2 prints (Box P 180, Folder 299)
    - Group Portraits - Friends - Reed, 1987; 2 prints (Box P 180, Folder 300)
    - Group Portraits - Friends - Fernando Romero, 1989; 4 prints (Box P 180, Folder 301)
    - Group Portraits - Friends - St. Barts, 17 prints (Box P 180, Folder 302)
    - Homes - Hudson Pines, New York, 8 prints (Box P 180, Folder 303)
    - Homes - Jordan Pond House - Dedication, 1982; 8 prints (Box P 180, Folder 304)
    - Homes - Ringing Point, 2 prints (Box P 180, Folder 305)
    - Homes - St. Barts, 1961; 1 print (Box P 180, Folder 306)
    - Homes - St. Barts - Oldenburg photos, 1980; 10 prints (Box P 180, Folder 307)
    - Homes - 10 West 54th Street - Housekeeper - Miss Orton, 1 print (Box P 180, Folder 308)
    - Relatives - Sydney Roberts, 1968; 2 prints (Box P 180, Folder 309)
  - Oversized, 25 prints
    - Margaret McGrath (Peggy) Rockefeller, 1 print (Box O 2)
    - DR - Business, 1 print (Box O 1)
    - DR - Business - Rockefeller Center - Edwin Dewees, 1985; 2 prints (Box O 1)
    - DR - Philanthropies, 7 prints (Box O 2)
    - DR - Portraits, 3 prints (Box O 1)
    - DR - Portraits, 1986-1987; 3 prints (Box O 2)
    - DR - Portraits (Box C 7)
    - David Rockefeller family, 1949; 4 prints (Box O 1)
    - David Rockefeller family, 2 glass plate negatives (Box O 3)
    - David Rockefeller family (Box C 5)